Now, let's take a closer look at the architecture of our project.
The entire system is designed around an end-to-end data pipeline.
We extract raw data from two primary sources: Last.fm and OpenWeatherMap.
This data is ingested directly into a multi-layered data lake structure...
...moving seamlessly from raw JSON formats to structured Parquet files.
Here, you can see how the file layers are organized.
We strictly separate them into raw, formatted, and combined stages...
...to ensure data consistency and high processing efficiency.
Next is our core logic: the CDI calculation formula.
CDI stands for City Depression Index, which measures a city's mood.
It uses the music's average valence as a baseline with environmental factors.