First, we can see that Docker is already running and in action.
Okay, so let's check it here.
And here, we need to change the time range.
Let's change it to May 1st, 2026, and click Update.
Right now, it's updating. Okay.
So here is the CDI World Map.
We selected 10 cities from all over the world to display our results.
Yes, and here...
It shows the CDI by City, and we also display these 10 cities here.
So you can see Sydney, San Paulo, Paris, Moscow, Berlin, New York...
...London, Tokyo, Mumbai, and Seoul.
Okay, and here...
We can track the CDI Over Time.
You can see the changes across these different cities.
Okay, and over here are the Highest CDI and Lowest CDI metrics.
If you click specifically on Sydney...
You can filter and see all the filtered data here.
Okay, so that's for that section.
Moving down, here is the Rainfall vs. CDI Trend.
You can find some correlations from this visualization over these dates.
So we can understand what is happening here.
Next to it is the Mood Distribution chart.
We can see the proportions for different mood categories.
And here is the City CDI Summary table.
You can see detailed statistics for the 10 cities, down to Mumbai.
Okay, and right here is the CDI Heatmap Calendar.
It lists the 10 cities with a clear color legend.
As the values change, you can track them here.
For instance, we find that Sydney might have better indexes here...
...while Paris shows a less ideal trend.