First, we can see that Docker is already running and in action.
Okay, so let's check it there.
And here, because we need to change it...
So change to May 1st, 2026, and right now, click Update. Okay.
Right now, it's updating. Okay.
So here is the CDI World Map.
We selected 10 cities from all over the world to display our results.
Yes, and here...
It shows the CDI by City, and we also display these 10 cities here.
So you can see Sydney, San Paulo, Paris, Moscow, Berlin, New York...
...London, Tokyo, Mumbai, and Seoul.
Okay, and here...
We can track the CDI Over Time.
You can see the changes across these different cities.
Okay, and over here are the Highest CDI and Lowest CDI metrics.
And also, if you click specifically on Sydney...
You can filter and see all the data displayed here.
Okay, so that's for that section.
Moving down, here is the Rainfall vs. CDI Trend.
You can find some correlations from this visualization over these dates.
So we can understand what is happening here.
Next to it is the Mood Distribution chart.
We can see the proportions for different mood categories.
And here is the City CDI Summary table.
You can see detailed statistics for the 10 cities, down to Mumbai.
Okay, and right here is the CDI Heatmap Calendar.
It lists the 10 cities with a clear color legend.
As the values change, you can track them here.
For instance, we find that Sydney might have better indexes here...
...while Paris shows a less ideal trend.
Pipeline Demonstration - Now, let's head over to the terminal.
We switch to the project directory and execute the main pipeline script.
Stage 1 begins: Ingesting weather data for the 10 global cities.
The script successfully fetches and saves real-time weather forecasts into raw JSON files.
Next, Stage 2 kicks off to fetch and format music data from Last.fm for each location.
It retrieves 50 tracks per city and logs specific music emotional attributes like sadder or happier.
In Stage 3, the pipeline combines the weather features and music metadata to calculate the CDI.
Finally, in Stage 4, it attempts to index and ingest this processed multi-source data directly into Elasticsearch.
The data has been successfully formatted and exported to the local path, completing the pipeline workflow!