Let me briefly walk you through the project structure.
The main entry point is run_pipeline.py, which runs the full workflow from ingestion to formatting, combination, and indexing.
The jobs folder contains most of the project logic, starting with the ingestion folder that collects raw data from the music and weather APIs.
The formatting folder cleans the raw JSON and converts it into Parquet, while the combination folder joins music and weather data by region and date.
It then calculates the City Depression Index, and the indexing folder sends the combined result to Elasticsearch.
The data folder works like a small data lake with three layers: raw, formatted, and combined.
The raw layer keeps the original API responses, the formatted layer stores cleaned Parquet files, and the combined layer stores the final joined data.
The dags folder contains the Airflow DAG, which shows how the pipeline can be scheduled automatically.
The docker folder has the Docker Compose file for Elasticsearch and Kibana, and the kibana folder stores the exported dashboard configuration.
The dashboard folder contains a standalone HTML version of the visualization that works without opening Kibana.
Overall, the project follows a standard data pipeline: collect, clean, join, calculate CDI, and visualize the result.